(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-28T00:52:20.029536",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
YouTube Music Weekendをご覧の皆さん！
Everyone watching YouTube Music Weekend!
こんにちは！
Hello!
いつだって We are...
Always, We are...
ReGLOSS！ hololive DEV_ISのReGLOSSです！
ReGLOSS! We are ReGLOSS from hololive DEV_IS!
YouTube Music Weekendをご覧の方は、私たちのことをご存知ない方も
Some of you watching YouTube Music Weekend might not know us yet,
いるかもしれないので、一人ずつ自己紹介からいきたいと思います！
so we'd like to start by introducing ourselves one by one!
イェーイ！
Yay!
じゃあ、奏ちゃんから！
Okay, Kanade-chan, you start!
はい！ドレミファソラシド♪ hololive DEV_IS所属
Yes! Do-Re-Mi-Fa-So-La-Ti-Do♪ From hololive DEV_IS,
ReGLOSSの音楽家、音乃瀬奏！
ReGLOSS's musician, Otonose Kanade!
イェーイ！
Yay!
そして！
And next!
はい！カワイイポジティブジーニアス、hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSSの
Yes! Cute Positive Genius, from hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS,
一条莉々華だよ！みんな、ヤッホー！元気ー？
Ichijou Ririka here! Yahoo, everyone! How are you doing?
元気だよー！
We're doing great!
そして！
And next!
はい、皆さんこんにちは。hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSSの賑やかしネタ枠担当、
Yes, hello everyone. I'm in charge of the lively comic relief for hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS,
十言われて一も問わない、全然威張らない、前髪ぐるぐるのお姉さんこと儒烏風亭らでん
Juufuutei Raden, the big sister with swirled bangs who never complains or acts haughty!
でございます。どうも！前髪前髪ぐるぐるぐるぐる...
Pleased to meet you! Bangs, bangs, swirl, swirl, swirl...
そして！
And next!
はーい！ぶんぶんばーん！hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSSの
Hi! Vroom vroom bang! From hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS,
轟はじめ、チョッちゃん、チョー、チョキ、はじめー！
Todoroki Hajime! Chocchan, Choo, Choki, Hajime!
いやー、昨年に引き続き、今年もYouTube Music Weekendに参加させていただけて
Wow, following last year, we're so honored to participate in YouTube Music Weekend again
とっても光栄です！
this year!
ちょっと噛んじゃった？
Did you stumble on your words a bit?
今噛んじゃったね。言い直す？
Yeah, I stumbled just now. Should I redub it?
うん、いいよいいよ！
Yeah, go ahead!
ふぅ... 昨年に引き続き、今年もYouTube Music Weekendに
Phew... Following last year, we are honored to participate in
参加させていただけて光栄です！
YouTube Music Weekend again this year!
イェーイ！え、みんな昨年何の曲やったか覚えてる？
Yay! Hey, does everyone remember what songs we performed last year?
『シンメトリー』！あ、『シンメトリー』やったね！
"Symmetry"! Ah, we did "Symmetry"!
『瞬間ハートビート』はやったっしょ！絶対やったよー！
We definitely performed "Shunkan Heartbeat"! Definitely!
デビュー曲だもんね！そして...
That's our debut song! And...
うん！もう1曲やってて、当時の新曲である『泡沫メイビー』も
Yeah! And we performed another song, our new release back then, "Utakata Maybe"!
披露させていただきました！懐かしい！
We performed it! So nostalgic!
ね、本当懐かしいね！超昔のことのように思えるし、
Right? Really nostalgic! It feels like so long ago,
当時はね、やっぱこういうステージに立つわけじゃなくて...
and back then, we weren't standing on a stage like this...
こう、なんていうか... 今見てこれ！凄くない！？
It was like... look around now! Isn't this amazing!?
お客さんがいる！凄い！ありがとう！
There's an audience! Amazing! Thank you!
ちょっとみんな、シーンとしないで！
Hey guys, don't go quiet on us!
大丈夫！画面の向こうで今めっちゃ盛り上がってくれてると思う！
Don't worry! I'm sure everyone behind the screen is hyping up right now!
真剣に見てくれてるんだよ！コメント頼むよー！
They're watching us intently! Leave some comments!
凄いね、カメラとかステージとかも進化して再び戻ってまいりました！
It's amazing how the cameras and stage evolved as we returned here again!
イェーイ！
Yay!
実はね、昨年から楽曲も増えまして！
Actually, we've released more songs since last year!
今年はいね、3月に『さくらミラージュ』、7月に『ミッドサマーストラスト』という
This year, we released "Sakura Mirage" in March and "Midsummer Stardust" in July!
楽曲をですね、リリースしてあります！
We've released these tracks!
また今年もこうして新しい曲を皆さんに披露することができて嬉しいね！
We're so happy to perform new songs for everyone again this year!
嬉しい！そしてそして！実は8月に、なななんと！
So happy! And that's not all! Actually in August, guess what!
メンバーたちのソロ曲を毎週連続リリースしていました！
We released our solo songs every week continuously!
イェーイ！
Yay!
らでんちゃんから！
Starting with Raden-chan!
はい！らでんです！らでんのソロ曲『おとしばなし』を
Yes! Raden here! My solo song, "Otoshibanashi",
リリースさせていただきました！なんと語りあり、
was released! It features narration,
言葉遊びあり、ラップありと、らでんらしさを
wordplay, and rap, packing all of Raden's style into it!
ギュッと詰め込んだ楽曲となっております！
It's a track packed with everything that makes Raden, Raden!
そしてね、実はこの要素もね、どこかにあったりするんですよ！
And actually, these elements might be hidden somewhere in the song!
え、気づかなかった！ちょっと探して聴いてみようかな！
Wait, I didn't notice! I'll look for them while listening!
ぜひ『おとしばなし』よろしくお願いします！
Please give "Otoshibanashi" a listen!
そして、らでんの次の週にリリースしたのは誰ー？
And who released their song the week after Raden?
はーい！
Me!
奏は『Cheerful Vibes Echo』という... 発音が良すぎて伝わらなかった
Kanade released a song called "Cheerful Vibes Echo"... My pronunciation was too good!
『Cheerful Vibes Echo』という楽曲をリリースしました！
I released a song called "Cheerful Vibes Echo"!
こちらの楽曲はですね、アコギがジャンジャカする感じの曲で、
This song features a strumming acoustic guitar,
すごくしっとりとした曲で、
and it's a wonderfully mellow tune,
朝とかに起きて聴くと「あぁ、今日もいい朝だな、頑張ろう」ってなれる
so when you wake up in the morning and listen to it, you feel like "Ah, what a nice morning, let me do my best!"
曲をですね、作らせていただきまして！
That's the kind of song we created!
奏もすごいニコニコしながら歌ったので元気が出る、そういう楽曲になっています！
I sang it with a big smile, so it's a song that brings you energy!
よかったら聴いてね！
Please check it out if you'd like!
そして奏の次は誰だー？
And who's next after Kanade?
はーい！莉々華の楽曲！
Me! Ririka's song!
タイトルが『ハピネス・フェノメノン』！
The title is "Happiness Phenomenon"!
いい女がもう全身から溢れ出ちゃうような、
A song where "fine woman" vibes overflow from my whole body!
そんな楽曲になっていて、もう聴くだけで気分アゲアゲ、自己肯定感アゲアゲな楽曲となってます！
Just listening to it raises your mood and boosts your self-esteem!
朝とかお昼とか「これから頑張るぞ！」みたいな時に聴いてね！
Listen to it in the morning or afternoon when you feel "Let's work hard!"
一緒に元気を出してもらえたらいいなと思っております！たくさん聴いてね！
I hope it gives you a boost of energy! Listen to it a lot!
以上でーす！
And that's all!
そして、最後は Hajime のソロ曲、「ビビデバ」でした！
And lastly, Hajime's solo song was "Bibiridabirira"!
なんでー！
Why?!
ビビデバ... ビビデラビディラ...
"Bibiridabirira"...
曲なんですけど、あの、すごいダンスナンバーで...
It's a song that's a real dance number...
こう、ドゥーンドゥーンって重低音がこうドゥンドゥン鳴ってて...
with heavy bass going "thump, thump"...
なんかこうサビに音数がちょっと少ないんだけど...
and in the chorus, the instrumentation is light,
静かな静寂の中で「アッ、アッ」ってなんか...
but in the quiet silence, there's like "ah, ah"...
ノッていく感じの、なんか Hajime 結構普段ダウナーなんですけど...
with a stylish vibe. Hajime is usually pretty low-key...
その夜のちょっとダウナーな静かな感じ？
so that quiet, low-key night vibe...
超その低音のガンガンっていうかっこよさが合わさった曲になってて...
combines super cool with heavy bass...
なんか、ちょっと夜に、ちょっと...
so, at night, when you're feeling a bit...
一人で聴いてほしいなーって。ラップとかダンスブレイクもあって...
I want you to listen to it alone. It also has a rap and a dance break...
あの、超かっこいい曲になっているのでぜひ聴いてください！
It turned out to be a super cool song, so please check it out!
聴いてくださーい！
Please listen to it!
なんかね、実はあれなんだよね。ソロ曲それぞれ、ま、時間帯が...
You know, actually, each solo song is set in a different...
変わっていくんだよね。Raden が夜明け前の曲で...
time of day. Raden's is before dawn...
Kanade が朝！
Kanade's is morning!
Ririka がお昼！
Ririka's is afternoon!
Hajime が夜。
Hajime's is night.
そう！だからね、ぜひあのこの順に聴くとね、ちょっとさらに深みが増すんじゃないかなーなんて思っております！
Right! So listening in this order might give it even more depth!
っていう感じね、それぞれ ReGLOSS のみんなの個性がたっぷり詰まった楽曲になっているので...
So with each song packed with ReGLOSS's unique personalities...
気になっていただけたら、なんと概要欄にね、リンクが貼ってありますので...
if you're interested, there are links in the description box...
そちらもぜひ聴いてみてください！
so please check those out as well!
聴いてねー！
Listen to them!
まあね、ある... MC 長げーよってもしかったら今思われてるかもしれないけど...
Well, people might be thinking "This MC segment is so long"...
もうちょい、もうちょいだけ喋らせてね。あの、このあとすぐに歌い出すんでね、ちょっと待ってね。
let us talk just a bit more. We'll start singing right after this, so please hold on.
いや、しかもですね、実は私達...
And actually, the thing is...
今年の9月で、なんとデビュー2周年を迎えます！
this September, we're celebrating our 2nd Anniversary since debut!
嘘！
No way!
そうなんだよ！しかも、デビュー2周年を迎えるということは...
That's right! And celebrating our 2nd Anniversary means...
3D の記念配信もあるということでーす！
we'll also have a 3D anniversary live stream!
初めて聞いた！
First time I've heard this!
そう、9月13日(土)の20時に 3D の記念配信があります！
Yes, on Saturday, September 13th at 8 PM, we'll have our 3D anniversary live stream!
何するのー？
What are we going to do?
まあやっぱり歌ったり踊ったりしちゃうんじゃない？
Well, we'll probably sing and dance, right?
漫才じゃないんですか？番長だけが踊る...
Is it not comedy stand-up? Only Bancho dances...
なんでだよ！みんなで踊って歌おうよ！
Why?! Let's all dance and sing together!
えー、どうしようかなー。だってみんなお揃いなんだよ。やるの？って何言ってるの！
Hmm, what should we do? Everyone's matching! What do you mean "Are we doing it?"!
漫才かなーと思って。漫才だと思ってたんだ。
I thought it was stand-up comedy. You thought it was stand-up?
冗談は置いておきつつ、この2年間ね、みんなにこうして見てもらうためにたくさん練習も重ねてきたので...
Jokes aside, over these two years, we've practiced a lot to show everyone...
ま、さらに去年よりもさらにパワーアップした姿をみんなにお見せできたらなと思っております！
so we hope to show you an even more powered-up version of ourselves than last year!
え、ちなみにさ、この1年でさ、なんか変わったこととかある？
By the way, has anything changed for you guys over this past year?
うわー、変わったこと... 何もかもが変わったけどね！
Whoa, what changed... Everything changed, though!
Kanade はさ、結構変わったのある？
Kanade, did you have anything big change?
ま、レッスンとか、なんかこう初めて 3D ライブ 1周年の時にやってさ...
Well, like lessons, when we did our 1st Anniversary 3D live for the first time...
踊りながら歌うのって大変だなーってすごい思ったの。
I realized how tough it is to sing while dancing.
立って歌うのだったらすごい得意なのかなって思ってたけど...
I thought I was really good if I was just standing and singing,
いざ体を動かしながら歌うってなると、なんか息が上がっちゃって難しいなーってなって...
but when moving my body while singing, I got out of breath, and it was hard...
そこからボイトレとかダンスレッスンとかを増やしてね...
So from there, I increased my vocal and dance lessons...
Kanade は実はかなり発声が変わりました！
and Kanade's vocal projection actually changed a lot!
すごい！最初からあんなに綺麗で歌うまだったのに...
Amazing! You were already so good and pretty at singing from the start...
よりグレードアップしたってことだよね！
so that means you leveled up even more!
そう、パワーアップしたので、よかったら見比べてみたりしてみてください！
Yes, I powered up, so please compare and watch!
見比べてください！これからも進化するぞー！
Please check it out! I'll keep evolving!
さすが歌柱！音柱じゃないや、歌柱！
As expected of the Song Hashira! Not Sound Hashira, Song Hashira!
音柱は本物のやつ...！
Sound Hashira is the real one...!
Hajime も新しいジャンルをちょっと...
Hajime also wanted to try a new genre...
入手したいなと思ってたんだけど...
and pick it up...
それを今年 2つ？チャレンジしてて...
and I've been challenging 2 new things this year...
1つは言ってたタップなんだけど、もう1個も別のジャンルを始めてみたりしてて...
One was tap dancing like I said, and I started another genre as well...
全然違うから、本当ゼロからのスタートみたいな感じなの。
It's totally different, so it really felt like starting from zero.
それをやっていって、またなんか...
And doing that, again...
3D ライブとかで披露できる時があったら、また進化してみせられるんじゃないかなと思って...
if there's a chance to perform it at a 3D live, I can show an evolved version of myself...
楽しみー！
Can't wait!
いいねー！じゃあ2人は得意なことをさらにまた...
Nice! So you two are taking what you're good at even further...
咲かせていくような感じで頑張ってるってことだよね？
So we're working hard with the feeling of blooming, right?
ねー！ / はい、リリカは、
Yeah! / Okay, for me, Ririka...
ちょっと心持ちが変わったなって思ってることがあって、
...there's something where I felt my mindset changed a bit.
最初本当にちょっとダンスが特に苦手すぎて、
At first, I was really, especially bad at dancing.
こういうライブとかみんなの前で踊るみたいな時に緊張だったり、
So during concerts like this, or dancing in front of everyone, I had a lot of nerves...
不安だったりとかいっぱいあったんだけど、
...and anxiety and things like that.
今回とある曲を踊らせていただいて、歌わせていただいたんですけど、
But this time, getting to dance and sing a certain song...
それを撮った時に、なんか、
...when we recorded it, somehow...
「不安だな」って気持ちより「一緒にやってて楽しいな」っていう気持ちの方が
...rather than feeling anxious, the feeling of "this is so fun to do together"...
なんか勝った気がして、
...felt like it won out!
「えー、嬉しい！」って思った！
And I thought, "Yay, I'm so happy!"
あら素敵じゃない奥さん！ / それ聞けたらこっちも嬉ちいよなぁ！
My, isn't that wonderful, ma'am? / Hearing that makes us happy too!
だからこれからもいっぱい歌って踊ってレッスンも頑張っていきたいと思います！
So I want to keep singing, dancing, and giving my all in lessons!
頑張ろう！頑張ろう！
Let's do our best! Let's do our best!
らでんちゃんはどう？ / らでんはさ、作詞にハマってさ、この1年で。
How about you, Raden-chan? / Raden got really into songwriting this past year!
で、自分でね、特にラップ？やっぱ言葉が好きなので、
And specifically, like, rap? Since I really love words,
特に日本語が好きで、それでちょっと何かやりたいなと思って、
...especially Japanese, I wanted to do something with that,
自作のラップ書いて、自分のチャンネルに投稿したりとか、
...so I wrote my own raps and posted them on my channel and stuff.
素敵だったよね！私たちの名前とかも入れてくれて。
It was wonderful! You even included our names.
自己紹介の歌がいっぱい！
Lots of self-introduction songs!
言葉と音楽みたいなところで自分で新しいチャレンジができたかなという1年でしたね。
In that overlap of words and music, I feel like I was able to take on new challenges this year.
すごーい！
Awesome!
みんなそれぞれにね、成長と挑戦を重ねた1年でございました。
It was a year where every one of us stacked up growth and challenges.
でもまだまだ伸び代もあるし成長できる部分いっぱいあると思うからこれからも頑張っていこうね！
But we still have plenty of room to grow, so let's keep doing our best!
頑張ろうー！ダンス頑張るよー！
Let's do our best! We'll work hard on dancing!
ということで今回は先日発表されました、私たちReGLOSSの新曲「Mid-Summer Citras」をこの後披露させていただきます！
So today, we're going to perform ReGLOSS's new song, "Mid-Summer Citras", which was recently announced!
イェーイ！
Yay!
3月にリリースした「拝啓、花吹雪」は春の訪れを感じられる楽曲だったと思いますが、
The song we released in March, "Hai-Kei, Hana-Fubuki", was a song where you could feel the arrival of spring,
今回の「Mid-Summer Citras」はタイトル通り...
...but this "Mid-Summer Citras" is, just like the title says...
夏ー！暑い！
Summer! So hot!
今これステージ立ってるけど日陰とかないから！日焼けやばいって！
We're standing on stage right now, but there's no shade! The sunburn is going to be crazy!
床絶対熱い！熱い熱い！
The floor is definitely hot! It's hot, it's hot!
でもやっぱReGLOSSが夏と一緒にここに帰ってきたっていう感じするよね！
But it really feels like ReGLOSS has returned here along with summer!
爽やかなメロディと、ちょっぴり強いリズムが、夏の暑さを吹き飛ばしてくれるような一曲になってます！
With its refreshing melody and slightly punchy rhythm, it's a song that blows away the summer heat!
みんなこの曲のイメージとか、レコーディングのエピソードとかある？
Does anyone have thoughts on the song's image or recording stories?
やっぱ夏だしすごい爽やかな曲だから、明るく楽しく爽やかにっていうのをすごいイメージしながら歌ったの覚えてる。
Since it's summer and a really refreshing song, I remember singing it while picturing bright, fun, and breezy vibes!
あーいいねー！確かにそんな感じだった！
Ah, nice! Indeed, it had that feeling!
はいはいはい！奏でもある！
Yes, yes, yes! Kanade has one too!
この楽曲のサビに「踊ってミッドサマー」っていうフレーズがあるんだけど、
In the chorus of this song, there's a phrase that goes "Odotte Mid-Summer"...
歌うま！ / ありがとう！
You're so good at singing! / Thank you!
その「サマー」をさ、奏ですごいリズムノリノリ乗るの好きだから、
And that "Summer", since Kanade loves getting really into the rhythm,
「踊ってミッドサンバ」ってやってて... / サンバ！？
...I was singing "Odotte Mid-Samba"... / Samba!?
「サンバ」ってやってたら、ディレクターさんにね...
I was singing "Samba", and the recording director told me...
「いやちょっとサンバすぎるんで、ちょっと調整して」って言われて歌ったの覚えてます。
"...Uh, that's a bit too much samba, so adjust it a bit, please."
めっちゃいいエピソードあるやん！初めて聞いたよそれ！
That's such a good story! That's the first time we've heard that!
初出しじゃん！ / はじめ振り付けで好きなとこがあって、
It's a reveal! / Hajime has a part of the choreography she likes...
やっぱサビの皆好きだと思うけど、こうで...
I think everyone likes the chorus part, doing this...
これ難しい...「踊ってミッド...」
This is tricky... "Odotte Mid..."
あのギコギコって動いてる、紐でギコギコ...
That clunky movement, like moving on strings, clunky, clunky...
これが楽しくてめっちゃ好き！
That's so fun and I love it!
バチッとはまるよね！らでんちゃんはどう？
It fits so perfectly! How about you, Raden-chan?
いっぱい練習しました！聴いてください！ダンスも歌もとにかく大変でした！聴いてください！
I practiced a lot! Please listen! Both the dancing and singing were super tough! Please listen!
はい！じゃあね、そんな「Mid-Summer Citras」、この後みんなに見てもらうと思うけど、もう早く見てもらいたいよね！
Alright! Well then, we're about to show everyone "Mid-Summer Citras", and we can't wait for you to see it!
そろそろMCだいぶ長いよね！喋りすぎた！
We've been talking for quite a while now! We talked too much!
なんかかなーっていう...なってる気がするよ、これ！
I feel like it's turning out that way!
じゃあ...
Alright...
はい！では、皆さんにもね、一緒に楽しんでもらえればと思います！
Alright! So, we hope everyone can enjoy it together with us!
行きますよ？ うん！
Here we go! - Yeah!
それでは... どうぞー！
And now... please enjoy!
ミッドサマーシトラス
[Song: Midsummer Citrus]
じゃんけんぽん！ あっち向いてホイ！
Rock, paper, scissors! Look that way!
やったー！ よっしゃー！
Yay! All right!
灼けつくような日差し
The scorching sunlight
水面に浮かぶスパンコール
Spangles floating on the water's surface
はしゃぐ夏色と逆光の裏側で
Behind the playful summer colors and backlighting
あの日の青春を呼び起こしてる
Recalling the youth of that day
デニムの裾を捲って
Rolling up the hem of my denim jeans
裸足で走ってる砂の上
Running barefoot on the sand
硝子の淵で回り回る
Spinning around the edge of glass
輝く瑠璃色のビー玉
A shining lapis lazuli marble
なんだか その笑顔と紙一重だ
Somehow, it's paper-thin close to that smile
フィルムを覗けばノンフィクション
Peeking through the film, it's non-fiction
彩りに解されたメモリー
Memories unraveled into color
リセットなんて出来ないから
Because there's no resetting it
love yourself just as you are now
踊ってミッドサマー アルゴリズムの中
Dance, midsummer, inside the algorithm
瞬息でダビングして
Dubbing in an instant
切り取って喜怒哀楽 これがきっと愛だ
Cropping out every emotion, this must be love
二度と忘れないように
So we never forget it again
le lemon lime orange キミといっしょうぶんの思い出
Le lemon lime orange, a lifetime of memories with you
何気ない一日が one of a kind
An ordinary day becomes one of a kind
弱気コンパクト閉じて
Closing the timid compact mirror
言葉を交わすリズムで
With the rhythm of exchanging words
氷が溶けては渦巻いた
The ice melted and swirled
魔法の杖がわりのマドラー
A stirrer acting as a magic wand
喉の奥くすぐる炭酸
Carbonation tickling the back of my throat
香る柑橘系のフレイバー
A fragrant citrus flavor
爽やかな気流にのって
Riding the refreshing air currents
波の還りを見守ってる beachside
Watching the waves recede by the beachside
あどけない面影に焦がれ
Yearning for an innocent visage
微かに触れそうな指先
Fingertips that almost touch
煌めきで上塗りしてしまおう
Let's coat over it with sparkle
get ahead of what you used to be
踊ってミッドサマー アルゴリズムの中
Dance, midsummer, inside the algorithm
瞬息でダビングして
Dubbing in an instant
切り取って喜怒哀楽 これがきっと愛だ
Cropping out every emotion, this must be love
二度と忘れないように
So we never forget it again
ミッドサマーシトラス oh yeah
Midsummer Citrus, oh yeah
いつだって we got love!! okay
Always, we got love!! okay
キミといるだけで feel so nice ココロはまた実り
Just being with you, feel so nice, my heart bears fruit once again
寝起きのご機嫌な太陽も 願ってもない燦々日和？
Even the cheerful sun just waking up, an unexpectedly glorious, sunny day?
白飛びしてしまうほど
Dazzling enough to cause whiteout
眩しいのは夏のせい
The dazzling light is summer's fault
踊ってミッドサマー アルゴリズムの中
Dance, midsummer, inside the algorithm
瞬息でダビングして
Dubbing in an instant
切り取って喜怒哀楽 これがきっと愛だ
Cropping out every emotion, this must be love
二度と忘れないように
So we never forget it again
le lemon lime orange キミといっしょうぶんの思い出
Le lemon lime orange, a lifetime of memories with you
何気ない一日が one of a kind
An ordinary day becomes one of a kind